{
	"a1.1": {
		"title": "add 1",
		"description": "Get 6 correct answers under 30 seconds. Two mistakes are allowed.",
		"time":  30,
		"mistakes": 2,
		"unlocks": ["a1.2"], 
		"data": [
			{
			"question": "1+1", 
			"answers":["1", "2"], 
			"solution": "2"
			},
			{
			"question": "2+1", 
			"answers":["3", "2"], 
			"solution": "3"
			},
			{
			"question": "3+1", 
			"answers":["5", "4"], 
			"solution": "4"
			},
			{
			"question": "4+1", 
			"answers":["3", "5"], 
			"solution": "5"
			},
			{
			"question": "5+1", 
			"answers":["6", "7"], 
			"solution": "6"
			},
			{
			"question": "6+1", 
			"answers":["1", "7"], 
			"solution": "7"
			},
			{
			"question": "7+1", 
			"answers":["8", "5"], 
			"solution": "8"
			},
			{
			"question": "8+1", 
			"answers":["9", "7"], 
			"solution": "9"
			},
			{
			"question": "9+1", 
			"answers":["1", "10"], 
			"solution": "10"
			}
		]
	},
	"a1.2": {
		"title": "add 2",
		"description": "Get 6 correct answers under a minute. Two mistakes are allowed.",
		"time":  60,
		"mistakes": 2,
		"unlocks": ["a1.3"], 
		"data": [
			{
			"question": "1+2", 
			"answers":["1", "3"], 
			"solution": "3"
			},
			{
			"question": "2+2", 
			"answers":["4", "2"], 
			"solution": "4"
			},
			{
			"question": "3+2", 
			"answers":["5", "4"], 
			"solution": "5"
			},
			{
			"question": "4+2", 
			"answers":["3", "6"], 
			"solution": "6"
			},
			{
			"question": "5+2", 
			"answers":["6", "7"], 
			"solution": "7"
			},
			{
			"question": "6+2", 
			"answers":["7", "8"], 
			"solution": "8"
			},
			{
			"question": "7+2", 
			"answers":["10", "9"], 
			"solution": "9"
			},
			{
			"question": "8+2", 
			"answers":["9", "10"], 
			"solution": "10"
			},
			{
			"question": "9+2", 
			"answers":["11", "10"], 
			"solution": "11"
			}
		]
	},
	"a1.3": {
		"title": "add 4",
		"description": "Get 6 correct answers under a minute. Two mistakes are allowed.",
		"time":  60,
		"mistakes": 2,
		"unlocks": ["a1.4"], 
		"data": [
			{
			"question": "1+4", 
			"answers":["5", "2"], 
			"solution": "5"
			},
			{
			"question": "2+4", 
			"answers":["8", "6"], 
			"solution": "6"
			},
			{
			"question": "3+4", 
			"answers":["5", "7"], 
			"solution": "7"
			},
			{
			"question": "4+4", 
			"answers":["4", "8"], 
			"solution": "8"
			},
			{
			"question": "5+4", 
			"answers":["9", "11"], 
			"solution": "9"
			},
			{
			"question": "6+4", 
			"answers":["12", "10"], 
			"solution": "10"
			},
			{
			"question": "7+4", 
			"answers":["8", "11"], 
			"solution": "11"
			},
			{
			"question": "8+4", 
			"answers":["12", "11"], 
			"solution": "12"
			},
			{
			"question": "9+4", 
			"answers":["13", "10"], 
			"solution": "13"
			}
		]
	},
	"a1.4": {
		"title": "add 3",
		"description": "Get 6 correct answers under a minute. Two mistakes are allowed.",
		"time":  60,
		"mistakes": 2,
		"unlocks": ["a1.4"], 
		"data": [
			{
			"question": "1+3", 
			"answers":["5", "4"], 
			"solution": "4"
			},
			{
			"question": "2+3", 
			"answers":["5", "6"], 
			"solution": "5"
			},
			{
			"question": "3+3", 
			"answers":["6", "7"], 
			"solution": "6"
			},
			{
			"question": "4+3", 
			"answers":["7", "8"], 
			"solution": "7"
			},
			{
			"question": "5+3", 
			"answers":["9", "8"], 
			"solution": "8"
			},
			{
			"question": "6+3", 
			"answers":["7", "9"], 
			"solution": "9"
			},
			{
			"question": "7+3", 
			"answers":["12", "10"], 
			"solution": "10"
			},
			{
			"question": "8+3", 
			"answers":["12", "11"], 
			"solution": "11"
			},
			{
			"question": "9+3", 
			"answers":["13", "12"], 
			"solution": "12"
			}
		]
	}
}
